

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

 $\mathsf{HTML}$ 

CSS

JavaScript(ES 6+)

React

Redux

JQuerv

Node

MySQL

MongoDB

**JSON** 

UI/UX

Firebase

MongoDB

Git

Materialize

Chrome DEV tools

**Project Management** 

Sales

**Customer Service** 

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

# CONTACT

P: (913) 375-8801 E: jakearagland@gmail.com W: https://raglandpc.github.io/My\_w ebsite/

#### SOCIAL

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jake-ragland-a65086a9/

# JACOB RAGLAND

## ASPIRING WEB DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I am a motivated and upbeat individual with high self-expectations for success. I have experience in sales, marketing, MERN full stack web development, statistics and have gained a wide range of working experience from diverse employers. My goal is to start a career in full stack web development, specify in Front End development and UI/UX design

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**MANAGER** 

Window Genie | Feb 2017 - Present

- Advised customers on the maintenance of their windows, gutters and the outside of their home.
- Interacted daily with office manager & staff to coordinate appointments.
- Proposed services to prospective & current customers.

**BRAND AMBASSADOR INTERN** 

James Hardie | Feb 2016 - Aug 2016

- Promoted James Hardie Building Products through marketing and direct sales
- Responsibilities included: generating incremental business growth through customer recruitment, product education, and increasing brand awareness through strategic marketing events.
- Developed and maintained relationships with contractors, retail stores and other business partners as part of a proactive marketing strategy

#### **EDUCATION**

CERTIFICATE, MERN FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

University of Kansas | 2018- 2018 GPA 4.0

BACHELOR OF ARTS, MAJOR ECONOMICS MINOR IN COMMUNICATION

University of Kansas | 2011 - 2015

### **APPLICATIONS BUILT**

Where the Show

Role: Project manager, UI developer and came up with the concept

Tropical Trivia

Role: Improve skills in HTML, CSS Bootstrap, JavaScript, and JQuery.

Train Scheduler

Role: Improve skills in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Moment.js, Firebase and

JQuery